<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fort</string>

    <!-- EditText Error Strings -->
    <string name="please_enter_name">Please enter Username</string>
    <string name="please_enter_email">Please enter Email</string>
    <string name="please_enter_mobile">Please enter Mobile</string>
    <string name="please_enter_valid_email">Please enter valid Email</string>
    <string name="please_enter_valid_mobile">Please enter valid Mobile</string>
    <string name="please_select_visitor_type">Please select visitor type</string>
    <string name="otp_didnt_match">OTP didn\'t match</string>


    <string name="activity_login_hint_full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="activity_login_hint_email">Email Address</string>
    <string name="activity_login_hint_mobile">Mobile</string>
    <string name="activity_login_button_submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="activity_login_text_i_agree">You agree to our Term and Condition and Privacy
        Policy
    </string>
    <string name="activity_login_text_check_term_condition">Please check our Term And Condition
    </string>


    <string name="activity_main_text_no_service_found">No Services Found</string>
    <string name="activity_main_text_powered_by">powered by</string>


    <string name="activity_exhibitor_list_title">EXHIBITOR LIST</string>
    <string name="activity_exhibitor_list_text_no_exhibitor_found">No Exhibitor Found</string>


    <string name="activity_event_list_text_no_programme_found">No Event Found</string>


    <string name="activity_session_list_text_no_session_found">No Session Found</string>


    <string name="activity_hall_plan_title">HALL PLAN</string>

    <string name="activity_my_favourites_title">MY FAVOURITES</string>

    <string name="activity_event_detail_title">EVENT DETAIL</string>

    <string name="activity_shop_online_title">Shop Online</string>
    <string name="activity_shop_online_back_button">Back</string>

    <string name="activity_brands_contact_details_title">BRANDS CONTACT DETAILS</string>


    <string name="activity_brand_list_title">Brand List</string>
    <string name="activity_brand_list_back_button">Back</string>


    <string name="activity_event_list_title">Event List</string>
    <string name="activity_event_list_back_button">Back</string>


    <string name="activity_information_title">About Us</string>
    <string name="activity_information_text_1">Gobindgarh Fort – the very symbol of Punjab. A symbol
        of the times when Punjab was forged. Spread across a grand 43 acres, right in the heart of
        Amritsar city, this magnificent, heritage site has a glorious history of its own, spanning
        across 257 years – right from the era of the Bhangi Misl to the time of Maharaja Ranjit
        Singh - to The British East India Company to The Indian Army to now, when finally, it opens
        its gates to the people of Punjab.</string>
    <string name="activity_information_text_2">The Punjab region in the 18th Century was ruled by
        clans called Misls. it was in the 1760s that Gujar Singh Bhangi,- a local chieftain- built
        this as a mud fortress- and it came to be known as “Bhagian da Qilla”. They owned it till
        1809 or for almost 49 years. However, the financial position of the misl deteriorated over
        time and by 1809 a minor ruler Gurdit S. Bhangi, a descendent of Gujjar Singh, was ruling
        Amritsar with the help of his mother Mai Sukhan. Mai Sukhan asked Arur Mal, a sahukar
        (trader)of the Bhangi township, to pay nazrana(Tribute). Not wanting to do so, Arur Mal
        migrated to the township of the rival Kanhiyas misl in order to avoid payment. At that time
        Maharaja Ranjit Singh was a rising star belonging to the Sukerchakia Misl. Arur Mal
        conspired with Shaikh Kamaluddin, a leading citizen and they invited Ranjit Singh, to take
        over the fort and the territories of Gurdit Singh. Maharaja Ranjit Singh was looking for
        just such an opportunity. He called upon Mai Sukhan to surrender a big cannon famously known
        as the Zamzama Cannon also known as “Bhangian di Tope”. Maharaja Ranjit Singh claimed that
        he had the right to the cannon as it was the Sukherchakia Misl’s share of the spoils of the
        war with the Afghan king, Ahmad Shah Durrani in 1765. The word Zamzama means “the Taker of
        Strongholds.” Mai Sukhan, refused. Ranjit Singh thereupon entered the city through the
        Ahluwalia gate. The Bhangies could not hold up again Ranjit Singh’s huge force.
        The Maharaja took over the fort and along with it the Zamzama Cannon and Mai Sukhan and the
        Bhangies were granted a few villages for their maintenance. it is stated that after winning
        the fort, Maharaja Ranjit Singh went to Shri Harmandir Sahib for a darshan and thanking to
        the supreme one and distributed positions to the residents of the town according to their
        merit. The capture of the fort was a valuable acquisition for Maharaja Ranjit Singh. He
        renamed the fort ‘Gobindgarh’ after the tenth Sikh Guru, Guru Shri Gobind Singhji. One of
        the main reasons for the consolidation of the fort most likely was to guard the city of
        Amritsar from invaders. This bean shaped city was most vulnerable to attacks and there were
        constant threats from the Afghans from the North West frontier. This positioning of the fort
        outside the historic walled city, unlike other forts in the centre of the historic cities,
        acted as an invincible barrier to get through to the pilgrim city The fort saw major
        repairs, additions and rebuilding from 1805 till 1809, under the supervision of its second
        governor and foreign minister of Maharaja Ranjit Singh, Fakir Azizuddin. Large sums of money
        were spent to make the fort a solid defence fortification with the help of the French
        Generals who had joined Maharaja Ranjit Singh.
        The Maharaja ruled successfully for forty years from the Sutlej to Indus, from Punjab Hills
        to Khyber Pass on the Indo-Central Asian Route Every year he spent some time at Amritsar for
        a change of climate and taking a bath in the holy tank. Generally, he reached Amritsar
        before the rainy season set in and remained there till the Dussehra celebrations were over.
        The Fort was captured by the British after the Second Anglo-Sikh War in 1849. After
        Independence the fort was garrisoned by the Indian army in 1947. Gobindgarh has been at the
        very heart of political events in the Punjab for most of its existence. Since it was always
        a military preserve, it was inaccessible for the common man. For almost a century it was
        hidden within a surrounding compound wall and concealed by trees and vegetation. More than
        any other military site Gobindgarh encapsulates the dramatic rise of Punjab, its golden days
        and then the collapse of the Sikh Kingdom when faced with the relentlessly expanding British
        Empire, till it’s independence. Finally, Recognizing the historic significance of this
        fortified precinct, in 2006 the Government of India handed over the vacant possession of the
        fort for protection and conservation to the Government of Punjab. It was declared as a
        historical monument by the Government of Punjab under The Punjab Ancient and Historical
        Monuments and Archaeological Sites and Remains Act, in 1964.
        This entire fort is currently being restored by the Government with the help of Asian
        Development Bank.</string>
    <string name="activity_information_text_3">Mayanagri World One Private Limited is Special
        Purpose Vehicle mandated by the Government of Punjab for Development, Operation and
        Maintenance of Virtual Reality Shows and Operation &amp; Maintenance of the Gobindgarh Fort,
        Amritsar on PPP Mode</string>


    <string name="activity_activities_title">Activities</string>
    <string name="activity_begin_tour_title">Begin Tour</string>


    <string name="dialog_text_quit_application">Do you want to quit the application?</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_auto_fill">Do you want to auto fill the details?</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_remove_favourite_exhibitor">Do you want to remove this exhibitor from
        your
        favourites?
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_add_favourite_exhibitor">Do you want to add this exhibitor to your
        favourites?
    </string>

    <string name="dialog_text_remove_favourite_programme">Do you want to remove this event from
        your
        favourites?
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_add_favourite_programme">Do you want to add this event to your
        favourites?
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_remove_favourite_session">Do you want to remove this session from your
        favourites?
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_add_favourite_session">Do you want to add this session to your
        favourites?
    </string>


    <string name="dialog_text_add_notes">Add Notes</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_enter_otp">Enter the OTP sent to your mobile number</string>


    <string name="progress_dialog_text_loading">Loading&#8230;</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_text_generating_survey">Generating Survey&#8230;</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_text_logging_out">Logging Out&#8230;</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_text_logging_in">Logging In&#8230;</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_text_please_wait">Please wait&#8230;</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_text_sending_request">Sending Request&#8230;</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_text_submitting_responses">Submitting Responses&#8230;</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_text_initializing">Initializing Application&#8230;\nThis may take
        some time
    </string>

    <string name="snackbar_text_no_internet_connection_available">No Internet Connection available
    </string>
    <string name="snackbar_text_error_occurred">Error Occurred</string>
    <string name="snackbar_text_exception_occurred">Exception Occurred</string>
    <string name="snackbar_text_invalid_access_pin">Invalid Access PIN</string>

    <string name="snackbar_action_go_to_settings">GO TO SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="snackbar_action_dismiss">DISMISS</string>
    <string name="snackbar_action_retry">RETRY</string>

    <string name="snackbar_action_undo">UNDO</string>


    <string name="dialog_text_new_version_available">New version of the application is available.
        Please update
    </string>


    <string name="dialog_hint_optional">optional</string>

    <string name="dialog_action_yes">YES</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_no">NO</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_cancel">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_save">SAVE</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_logout">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_resend_otp">RESEND OTP</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_proceed">PROCEED</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_ignore">IGNORE</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_update">UPDATE</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_close">CLOSE</string>
    <string name="dialog_action_show_all">SHOW ALL</string>


    <string name="facebook_app_id">1050784248336887</string>


</resources>
